this is a really fast video I've been
going through comments on YouTube yes I
actually read your comments these days
and I really am going to I feel sorry
just Nala whoever you are I'm not
calling you out specifically I'm trying
not to because but this this comment
illustrates the point I was trying to
make about the most important thing
people can learn and I really really
want to hit this point home you're going
to see lots of videos from me about this
I've now made this my number one thing
to focus on and I I fail at it too all
the time this is why it's also a
reminder to me when you read the comment
it says I'm going to just read it I do
not know how I got this video
recommended the author is definitely
very gifted I understand happen what he
said and his content I guess it must be
the right stuff PS I think this I think
I need a beginner's course for bash
stuff he goes way too fast for
me anybody who knows me knows I mean my
entire story just Google it I don't have
to do it and the point is one Google
search one quick Google search for RDX
Rob courses RDX Rob or anything like
that and they would have answered this
question entirely and they would have
found the beginner course material they
would have seen everything and they
wouldn't have had to answer
it there is a time when [__] Rob
would have pushed back on somebody like
this and said have you bothered reading
the title have you bothered Googling
that let me Google that for you the
disease is that people I don't know how
good people good people have lost the
ability or never learned the ability to
answer their own questions given all of
the AI all of the amazing search enges
are out there and we have people who
just don't even bother to lift a finger
to answer their own
questions and I I use I call it
intellectual laziness which sounds
pejorative and mean but that's what this
is this is what we have to fight against
we have to get and that goes for me
somebody called me out and said you know
yeah stupid video could have Google that
on rust on the first day and then the
apology not accepted I'm like you know
what you're right you're being a dick
about it and because they then proceeded
to recommend R of
course but the problem is that that any
of us who doesn't we should be focusing
on answering our own questions and
getting good at answering our questions
and using every tool at our disposal
every Community member at our disposal
to do that and that should be a reflex
The Reflex shouldn't be yell over the
cubicle wall at the person next to you
to get your answer